Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Teamster Election Files, 1991-1996; Series 8; 12 Linear Feet
  - 1996 Election, 1976-1998; Series 8 Subseries 2
    - 1989- IBT Small Package Workshop, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - UPS Strike 1993, 1993-1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - UPS One Day Strike- 776, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - UPS Atlantic Area Grievance Panel, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - UPS Strike- Lawsuit, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - 1993- Eastern Conference of Teamsters (ECT) Small Package, 1993 May; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - 1992- Transition Report, 1992 April 27; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Welcome to the Teamsters, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Original Box List for 1996 Rerun Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Official IBT Election 1996, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - 1996- IBT Delegate Election, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Rules- 1996 IBT Election, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Teamster Magazine, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Official Propaganda, 1994-1995, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Official Propaganda, 1995 February; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Protests, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Protests, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Protests, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - TDU/IBT 1996 Election, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - TDU- 1996 Election, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - TDU Activist, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Convoy- Dispatch, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Convoy/Dispatch, 1995-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - TDU Internal Criticism, 1976, 1980, 1992, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Other Left Journals, 1993, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Letter to Editor/In These Times, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Editor/The Nation Labor Notes, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Union Democracy Review, 1994-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - In These Times, 1993-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Labor Notes, 1992, 1994-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - TDU-IBT Analysis, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Carey- The Mob, 1995, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Carey- The Mob, 1993-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Carey- The Mob, 1993-1994, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Carey- Moroney, 1994-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Carey/Congress, 1993, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - "Suppressed", 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Early Carey, 1966, 1968; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Carey- UPS Stock, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Carey- Time Magazine, 1992-1995; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Carey- Real Estate, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Immunity Agreement, 1987 November 20; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Carey- Independent Review Board (IRB) Decision- Press, 1992-1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Carey- Geller Letters, 1993-1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Carey- 804 Pension, 1989; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Carey- The Will, 1994, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Carey- IRB Decision, 1993-1994, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Carey- Locals 295/851 Genoese, 1993-1994; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Hoffa, Jr., 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Hoffa Junior's Ties to Employer, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Hoffa- Legacy of Corruption Earlier Version, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Carey Campaign Literature, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Morris- 1996, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Morris/IRB/Declaration, 1994 June 30; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Carey Ticket, 1994-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Carey Ticket Propaganda, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Carey Ticket/November Mailings, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Putting Members First, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Carey Activist Memo, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Carey Ticket Candidates, 1993, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - HoffaScams, 1995-1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Update on Teamster Reform, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - HoffaWatch, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Jr. Hoffa Team, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Carey Action Fax, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - 1998 Rerun Election, 1987-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3; 1.5 Linear Feet
    - Original Box List for 1998 Rerun Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - November Rerun Plan, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - GEB Protest, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Cost of Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Cherkasky- Rerun Schedule, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - 1998- New Nominations, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Election Officer Debate, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Cherkasky, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Research/Congress- Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Court Filings- Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Acting Election Officer (EO)- 45 Day Delay, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Department of Justice (DOJ)- Union Run Election, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Court Filings- Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Court Filings- Rerun Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Quindel- Report/Rerun, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Rerun- Official Filings, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Teamster Magazine, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Teamster Magazine, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Teamster Magazine, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Stand-Up Leaflets, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia Leaflets, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Stand Up Leaflets, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Hamilton/Pico Protest, 1999 February 2; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - May 3- Philadelphia Rally, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Clark- Leave of Absence, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Joint Council (JC) 53, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Joint Council 53, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Philadelphia HoffaNow Office, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Philadelphia Mailing, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia Fundraiser- February 7, 1998, 1998 February 7; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania (PA) Conference- Blind Mailings, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - PA Conference Blind Mailings, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Western PA- JC 40, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - JC 53- Anti Morris Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Central PA Phone Bank, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - 1996/1998- Worksites, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - 1996/1998- Worksites, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - 1996/1998- Worksites, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - 1996/1998- Worksites, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Expenses- John Steger Rerun, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Expenses- John Steger Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Expenses- John Steger Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Expenses- John Steger Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Expenses- John Steger Rerun, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Central PA- Mailings, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Central PA Mailings, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Central PA Mailings, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Central PA- Mailings, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Central PA Mailings, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Central PA- Mailings, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Central PA- Hoffa, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Central PA- Hoffa, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Rerun Election- Patriot News, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Hoffa- Harrisburg Visit, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - 776- Rite Aid, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Freight Dues, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Deaner- Mailing List, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Central PA Phone Banking, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Candidate Mailings- Central PA, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Central PA- Esquire Mailing, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Leedham Visit- August 1998, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Central PA Flyers, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Expenses- DeSanti Campaign, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Expenses- DeSanti Campaign, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Expenses- National Campaign, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Deaner- Contributions, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Decision- Leedham Protest, 1999 1999 January 28; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Leedham Protest, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Leedham Protest, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Leedham Protest Election Appeals Master, 1999 February 23; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Rerun Protest Decision- Press, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - HoffaNow Press Releases, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Rerun Ballot Count- Security, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Conboy Decision- Leedham Protest, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Press- Conboy Decision- Leedham, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Edelstein Decision- Leedham, 1999 March 1; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Edelstein Decision- Press, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Leebove Investigation, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Cherkasky Certification, 1999 March 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Government Position on Certification, 1999 March 12; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Hoffa Position on Leedham Protest US Court, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Swearing In- Hoffa Unity Slate, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Swearing In- Hoffa Unity Slate, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Inaugural Number Two, 1999 April 2; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Hoffa Certification- Press, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Original Box List for 1998 Rerun Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Southern Rerun Election, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Southern Rerun Election, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Ballot Count- 1998, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Hoekstra- Goodling, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - February 1999- Hoekstra Report, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Hoekstra Report- Democratic Rebuttal, 1999 March 4; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Hoekstra Report, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - IBT Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Hoekstra- May, June, July- 1997, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Hoekstra- November/December 1997, 1997 November-December; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Hoekstra- February 1998, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - May 19, 1998, 1998 May 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - May 19, 1998, 1998 May 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - May 19, 1998- Hoekstra, 1998 May 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - May 19, 1998, 1998 May 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - June 1998, 1998 June; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Hoekstra- IRB July 1998, 1998 July; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - July 1998, 1998 July; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - September/October- 1998, 1998 September-October; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Setpember 1998- Diamond Walnut Strike, 1998 September; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Hoekstra November/December 1998, 1998 November-December; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Hoekstra- August/September 1997, 1997 August-September; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Hoekstra- October 1997, 1997 October; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - 3/26/1998- Hoekstra, 1998 March 26; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - 3/26/1998- Hoekstra, 1998 March 26; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Hoekstra- March 1998, 1998 March; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - 4/29/1998- Hoekstra, 1998 April 29; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - 3/26/1998- Hoekstra, 1998 March 26; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Hoekstra- April 1998, 1998 April; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - April 1998, 1998 April; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - 4/30/1998- Hoekstra, 1998 April 30; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Transition, 1998 December 8; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Transition Team Updates, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - March 6- Inaugural, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - January 1998, 1998 January; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - February 1998, 1998 February; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - March 1998, 1998 March; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - April 1998, 1998 April; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - May 1998, 1998 May; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - June 1998, 1998 June; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - July 1998, 1998 July; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - August 1998, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - September 1998, 1998 September; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - October 1998, 1998 October; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - November 1998, 1998 November; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - December 1998, 1998 December; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - December 1998, 1998 December; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - December 1998, 1998 December; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Election Officer's Final Report on Election Procedures: Volume I, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Election Officer's Final Report on Election Procedures: Volume II, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Election Officer's Final Report on Election Procedures: Volume III, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Original Box List for 1998 Rerun Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - TDU- Labor Notes, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - TDU- Labor Notes, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - TDU and Labor Notes, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - TDU- Labor Notes, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - TDU- Labor Notes, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - TDU Homepage, 1998 September 1-2; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - 1998- TDU Convention, 1998 November 6-8; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - 1997- TDU Convention, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - TDU Convention- 1998, 1998 November 7-8; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Scandal Propanganda, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - AUD, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - In These Times, 1997-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - The Nation, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Scandal and the Left, 1997 December 29; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Scandal and the Left, 1996-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Scandal and 'Left', 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Scholars, Artists, and Writers for Social Justice (SAWSJ)- 1998, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Metz- LM-2- Local 610, 1996-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Metz- LM-2- JC 13, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Metz Slate- Nominations, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Metz Slate, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Leedham Activist Mailing September, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Leedham- Flyers, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Leedham Slate, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Kroger 'Reopener', 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Leedham Slate- Nominations, 1998 June; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 31)
    - Local 177, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 32)
    - Leedham- Sever Protest, 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 88, Folder 33)
    - Leedham Research, 1998 August 12; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Local 705, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Leedham/Sever Decision, 1998 August 14; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Leedham $100,000 Club, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - EO- Leedham Guilty, 1998 October 13; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Leedham- LM-2- Local 206, 1994-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Morris- Rerun, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Morris- Smear Literature, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - 1996- Morris- Failure Fax, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Metz- Contract St. Louis Post-Gazette, 1997 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Theodus Slate, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Padellaro LM-2's, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Ken Hall, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Ken Hall, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Ken Hall, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Geller- IRB, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Lawsuit to Recover IBT Funds, 1997 December 22; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - EO- Salmeron, 1998 April 27; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Hoffa Finances- 'Cleared', 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - EO- Hoffa Cleared, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Independent Financial Auditor, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - IBT Finances- Hoekstra, 1998 March 26; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - IBT Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Teamster Finances, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - 1997- LM-2, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - 1998- IBT LM-2, Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Detroit News Strike, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Detroit News Strike, 1995-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - August 1998- Magazine 'Ad', 1998 August; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - October/November 1998 Magazine Ads, 1998 October-November; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Hoffa- Spanish Literature, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - DeSanti Campaign Meeting June 17, 1998, 1998 June 17; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Aaron Belk, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Jack Cipriani, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Local 391- Poll, 1998 October 13; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Daugherty Protest, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Black Caucus, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - HoffaNow- Chicago, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Washington, DC Fundraiser, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Brick, New Jersey (NJ)- Fundraiser, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Scandal- Hoffa Files, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Aprl 27- Washington, DC Rally, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - New York City (NYC)- Labor Day Rally, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Hoffa- Labor Day- NYC, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - July 12- NJ Fundraiser, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Brigantine Rally, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Middletown, New York (NY)- Fundraiser, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Leedham Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - National Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Hoffagrams- HoffaNow, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Hoffagrams- HoffaNow, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Hoffa Grams- HoffaNow, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 21)